(Bernadette:)Why does this bother you so much?
(Penny:)I don't know. It's just, he's so passionate
about so many different things.
(Penny:)I just don't get that way. Do you?
(Bernadette:)Well, sure.
I'm pretty passionate about science.
(Bernadette:)I remember the first time I looked through
a microscope and saw tiny microorganisms.
(Bernadette:)It was like a whole other universe.
(Bernadette:)If I wanted to, I could wipe it out
with my thumb like a god.
See, I wish I had
some of that fire in my life.
I wanna care about things
and get excited like you guys.
(Bernadette:)- There's no reason you can't.
- You think?
Absolutely. All we need to do is spend time
and find something you're passionate about.
(Penny:)Ugh, that sounds like a lot of work.
(Howard(onwebcam):)Hey, what's up?
(Raj:)Lucy's coming over. I need some advice.
(Howard:)However long you think
the foreplay should be, triple it.
(Raj:)Just tell me which one you think
is more manly.
This hockey jersey or this football jersey?